<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Text Analysis on Anything is |Data| is Anything</title>
    <link>/categories/text-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Text Analysis on Anything is |Data| is Anything</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/text-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ctextclassics, my First Package</title>
      <link>/blog/2018-05-17-ctextclassics-my-first-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018-05-17-ctextclassics-my-first-package/</guid>
      <description>My latest update is a big one - a milestone! I have authored my first ever R package, available on my Github! It is an API caller for ctext.org, a site that hosts numerous pre-modern Chinese texts. The scope is broad, but think philosophical works in Confucianism, Daoism, Legalism, military doctrines, history compilations, works in medicine, and many more.
I’ve indexed at least 130 individual works and I’ll keep an eye out for more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scraping for a Booklist of the Chinese Classics</title>
      <link>/blog/2018-05-08-scraping-for-a-booklist-of-the-chinese-classics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018-05-08-scraping-for-a-booklist-of-the-chinese-classics/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was considering a project that would be interesting and unique. I decided I would like to do a text analysis on classical Chinese texts, but wasn’t sure what kind of analysis regarding which texts. I decided to keep it small - and use five of the “core” Chinese classics - The Analects, The Mengzi, Dao De Jing, Zhuangzi, and Mozi. While there are many books in Confucianism, Daoism, and Moism, these texts are often used as the most representative examples of each “genre”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>